(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T22:38:36.506393",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
聖なる夜
Holy night.
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now,
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's leap forth!
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine brightly,
ハート きゅんって Pump it up
making hearts throb, pump it up!
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先まで
Hyper Jumpin'! Beyond our dreams,
もっと もっと 刺激が欲しいの
we want more and more excitement!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin'! Even across the sea!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a concert where we can be together.
３６０度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
Higher and higher, I want to fly!
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Now, Hyper Jumpin'! Let me jump over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Getting high until we turn to dust,
ダンシング Shake it up
dancing, shake it up!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' Now
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert you watch, to a concert where you meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night.
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now,
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's leap forth!
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine brightly,
ハート きゅんって Pump it up
making hearts throb, pump it up!
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先まで
Hyper Jumpin'! Beyond our dreams,
もっと もっと 刺激が欲しいの
we want more and more excitement!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin'! Even across the sea!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a concert where we can be together.
３６０度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from everywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
Higher and higher, I want to fly!
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Now, Hyper Jumpin'! Let me jump over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Getting high until we turn to dust,
ダンシング Shake it up
dancing, shake it up!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' Now
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert you watch, to a concert where you meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...a miracle begins.
さあ！
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで 楽しんでいこう
Getting high until we turn to ash, let's enjoy it!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin'! Even beyond the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
...it's a live event where we can be together.
３６０度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
We're right here. Close enough to touch.
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert you watch, to a concert you meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...a miracle begins.
さあ！
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで 楽しんでいこう
Getting high until we turn to ash, let's enjoy it!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin'! Even beyond the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
...it's a live event where we can be together.
３６０度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
We're right here. Close enough to touch.
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert you watch, to a concert you meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
聖なる夜 4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
Holy night, when four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over!
ハイになって ハイになるまで 達していこう
High in the sky, let's reach until we burn out!
Hyper Jumpin'
虹の向こうまでもっと
Farther beyond the rainbow, even more,
近づきたいの
I want to get closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you could almost touch.
ねぼらぼライブ Re:VISION
Neborabo Live Re:VISION
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
2025.12.21 Sun
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live to watch, to a live to meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over!
ハイになって ハイになるまで 達していこう
High in the sky, let's reach until we burn out!
Hyper Jumpin'
虹の向こうまでもっと
Farther beyond the rainbow, even more,
近づきたいの
I want to get closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you could almost touch.
ねぼらぼライブ Re:VISION
Neborabo Live Re:VISION
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
2025.12.21 Sun
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live to watch, to a live to meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over!
ハイになって ハイになるまで 達していこう
High in the sky, let's reach until we burn out!
Hyper Jumpin'
虹の向こうまでもっと
Farther beyond the rainbow, even more,
近づきたいの
I want to get closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
A live concert where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you could almost touch.
ねぼらぼライブ Re:VISION
Neborabo Live Re:VISION
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
2025.12.21 Sun
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live to watch, to a live to meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで 楽しんでいこう
Until we get high and turn to ash, let's enjoy ourselves!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even across the sea!
もっともっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer.
みるだけじゃない
Not just something to watch—
いっしょになれるライブ
a live show where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher.
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. Close enough to reach out and touch.
ねぼらぼライブ Re:VISION
NePoLaBo Live Re:VISION
2025.12.21 Sun
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show you can meet at.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで 楽しんでいこう
Until we get high and turn to ash, let's enjoy ourselves!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even across the sea!
もっともっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer.
みるだけじゃない
Not just something to watch—
いっしょになれるライブ
a live show where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher.
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. Close enough to reach out and touch.
ねぼらぼライブ Re:VISION
NePoLaBo Live Re:VISION
2025.12.21 Sun
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show you can meet at.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on...
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's leap over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to dust,
楽しもう
let's have fun!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' across the sea,
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer.
Woh...
ドキドキしたい
I want my heart to throb,
Gimme Gimme Gimme 愛
Gimme Gimme Gimme love!
Woh...
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher.
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' now
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show where you can meet.
聖なる夜
On a holy night,
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
when four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on...
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's leap over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to dust,
楽しもう
let's have fun!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' across the sea,
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer.
Woh...
ドキドキしたい
I want my heart to throb,
Gimme Gimme Gimme 愛
Gimme Gimme Gimme love!
Woh...
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher.
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' now
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show where you can meet.
聖なる夜
On a holy night,
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
when four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on...
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's leap over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to dust,
楽しもう
let's have fun!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' across the sea,
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer.
Woh...
ドキドキしたい
I want my heart to throb,
Gimme Gimme Gimme 愛
Gimme Gimme Gimme love!
Woh...
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher.
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close I could almost touch you.
Hyper Jumpin' now
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show where you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to ash!
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the sky!
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A concert where we can be together
３６０度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
ドキドキしたい Gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to throb, gimme gimme gimme love!
もっと
More...
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
Right here. So close you could almost touch.
聖なる夜
Holy night
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and turn to ash!
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to the other side of the sky!
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A concert where we can be together
３６０度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
ドキドキしたい Gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to throb, gimme gimme gimme love!
もっと
More...
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even higher!
ピンポンパンポーン
Ding-dong-dang-dong
みなさん、メリークリスマス！
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
本日は「ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to "Nepolabo Live re:VISION" today!
ライブ開始はこの後、19:00からの予定となっていますので、今しばらくお待ちください。
The concert is scheduled to start after this at 19:00, so please wait a moment.
本公演のチラ見せ部分は、動画のYouTubeへの投稿が可能です。
Posting video clips of the sneak peek portion of this performance to YouTube is permitted.
が！
But!
しかし！他のSNSは音声なしの30秒以内の動画の投稿をお願いします。
However! For other SNS, please post videos under 30 seconds without audio.
静止画のスクリーンショットや感想などは全編を通じて可能なので、いっぱい呟きお願いします！
Screenshots and impressions are allowed throughout the entire event, so please tweet a lot!
はーい！
Okay!
禁止事項ですが、本公演のミラー配信、並びに音声ありのライブ本編動画の一部SNSへの投稿となっています。
As for prohibited actions, mirror streaming and posting live show videos with audio to certain SNS are prohibited.
音声なしでも30秒を超える動画のSNS投稿も禁止となっています。
Posting videos exceeding 30 seconds to SNS, even without audio, is also prohibited.
ルールを正しく守ってライブを楽しんでください。
Please follow the rules properly and enjoy the live show!
ねぇ
Hey,
さぁ
So then,
みんな〜
everyone~
遊びに来る準備は出来てるかな？
Are you ready to come play?
ねねが描いた服着てる人いるかなー？
Is anyone wearing the outfit Nene designed?
雪民さんたちがどんな姿で会いに来てくれるか楽しみ！
I'm excited to see what kind of avatars the Yukimin come as!
ホロアースのライブだから好きな服装でライブ見れるのもいいよねー
Since it's Holoearth, it's great being able to watch in whatever outfit you like!
スクショも撮っていいみたいなのでいろんな角度からたくさん撮ってほしいです！
Looks like taking screenshots is allowed, so please take lots from all angles!
そう！普通のライブだと動いて見て回ったりは出来ないもんね！
Yeah! At a normal concert, you can't walk around and look, right?
みんなの最高の写真期待してるぞー！
We're looking forward to your best photos!
と言うわけでライブ開始までもうしばらくお待ちください！
So then, please wait a little longer until the concert starts!
一緒にライブ盛り上がっていこう！
Let me hear you get hyped up together!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ねぼらぼライブ Re:viSiON 始まるぞー！
Nebolabo Live Re:viSiON is starting!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ちょっと早めのクリスマス！盛り上がっていくぞー！
A slightly early Christmas! Let me hear you get hyped!
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び出そう
Let's jump out
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine bright
ハート きゅんって Pump it up
Make hearts flutter, pump it up
Hyper Jumpin'
夢の先まで
Beyond your dreams
もっと
More
刺激が欲しいの
I want excitement
(ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！)
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!)
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
(ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！)
(Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!)
Hyper Jumpin'
子どもくらいはしゃぐ方が お得でしょう
It's better to go wild like kids
(ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！)
(Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!)
低気圧から 爬い上がっていく テンション
Tension rising up from low pressure
(ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！)
(Polka! Polka! Polka!)
酔いながら打ち返しまくる @メンション
Replying to @mentions while tipsy
(ラミィ！ラミィ！ラミィ！)
(Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!)
カートを乗りこなして進む ミッション
Driving the cart through the mission
(ぼたん！ぼたん！ぼたん！)
(Botan! Botan! Botan!)
このままスピード加速して
Speeding up just like this
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
Wonder what lies at our destination
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Unstoppable feelings getting a running start
次元を超えて行こう
Let's cross dimensions
行こう！
Let's go!
さぁ
Now then
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び跳ねよう
Let's leap high
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and burn to ashes
ダンシング Shake it up
Dancing, shake it up
Hyper Jumpin'
空の向こうまで
To the other side of the sky
もっと
More
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer
Woh...
ドキドキしたい
Want my heart to throb
Gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme gimme gimme love
Woh...
もっと
Higher
高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher
(ハイ！)
(Hey!)
360度楽しめてるかー？！
Are you enjoying the 360-degree view?!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
(ハイ！)
(Hey!)
(みんなー！みてるー？！)
(Is everyone watching?!)
(ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！)
(Hey! Hey! Hey!)
Hyper Jumpin'
斜めから攻めて解決 クエスチョン
Solving questions by attacking from an angle
(ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！)
(Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!)
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれる チェーンソー
A chainsaw cutting through negativity
(ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！)
(Polka! Polka! Polka!)
流れるコメントと掛け合い セッション
Call-and-response session with live comments
(ラミィ！ラミィ！ラミィ！)
(Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!)
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つ フリックショット
Honing aim to snipe with a flick shot
(ししろ！ぼたん！)
(Shishiro! Botan!)
Disは NO NO
Disrespect is NO NO
好きなら MORE MORE MORE
If you like it, MORE MORE MORE
邪魔するノイズは
Distracting noise
打ち消せ BANG BANG BANG
Cancel it out BANG BANG BANG
遊びたいだけ
Just want to have fun
アンチは無視して
Ignore the haters
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴っ飛ばせ
Kick it away
Jump around!
このまま僕らは旅をして
Continuing our journey like this
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
Wonder what lies at our destination
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking with the future we believed in
次元を超えて行こう
Let's cross dimensions
さぁ
Now then
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's jump across
ハイになって
Getting high,
灰になるまでのダンシング
dancing until we turn to ashes!
Shake it up!
Hyper Jumpin'
ビルの向こうまでも
Even beyond the buildings,
もっともっと
more and more,
近づきたいの
I want to get closer!
Woh...
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want to feel my heart pound, gimme gimme gimme love!
Woh...
もっともっと
More and more,
高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher!
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
Hi! Hi! Hyper Jumpin' Now!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
みんな元気ー？
Is everyone doing great?
元気ー！
Doing great!
というわけで、自己紹介行きましょう！
Alright then, let's start off with self-introductions!
ねねちからー！
Starting with Nenechi!
じゃあみんな、アイテムとかの準備いいですかー？
So everyone, are you ready with your items and stuff?
順番に行きますからね！みんなアイテムの準備してください！
We'll go in order, so everyone, please prepare your items!
そう！「ね・ぼ・ら・ぼ」で行くからね！
That's right! We'll go in the order of "Ne-Bo-Ra-Bo"!
どれくらい待つ？この準備。
How long should we wait for them to prepare?
ちょっと待った方がいいか。
Should we wait a little bit?
ちょっとじゃあ、ショートカットにペンライト入れるなりしてね。
Put your glowsticks into your shortcut slots,
1, 2, 3, 4でこう、取り出してね。
so you can pull them out with 1, 2, 3, 4.
4, 3, 2, 1, はい！どうぞ！ねねさん！
4, 3, 2, 1, alright! Go ahead, Nene-san!
はい！じゃあみんな行くよー！
Okay! Here I go, everyone!
コンねねー！ホロライブ5期生、ねぼらぼの、みんなの心の…
Kon-Nene~! Hololive 5th Gen, NeBoRaBo's, and everyone's hearts'...
せーの！
Ready, set!
エナジードリンク！
Energy Drink!
桃鈴ねねでーす！よろしくねー！
I'm Momosuzu Nene~! Nice to meet you!
じゃあ次！切り替えて！
Next up! Switch over!
尾丸ポルカだよーー！
It's Omaru Polka~~!
いつものないか。ポルカおるかー？
Oh, we don't have the usual call? "Is Polka here~?"
おるよー！
She's here!
はい！ねぼらぼの「ポ」！尾丸ポルカでーす！よろしくー！
Yes! NeBoRaBo's "Po", Omaru Polka here! Nice to meet you!
こんなみー！
Kon-Lamy~!
ホロライブ5期生の、雪花ラミィです！
From Hololive 5th Generation, I'm Yukihana Lamy!
ラミィちゃん好きー！
We love you, Lamy-chan!
愛してるよー！
I love you!
ラミィもだよー！
Lamy loves you too!
はい！そして…最後！
Okay! And... last up!
はい、みんな準備してる？
Hey, is everyone ready?
何をも？
For what?
準備してる？
Are you ready?
してるよー！
We are!
スタンプスタンプ！スタンプあるでしょ！
Stamps, stamps! You have stamps, right?
ららーい！ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんです！
La-la-i! Hololive 5th Gen, Shishiro Botan here!
有料いただきましたー！いただきますよー！
Paid stamps received! Thank you so much!
はい！
Alright!
皆さんね、ばっちり決まったところで、新しい試み Re:VISION ライブということで…
Now that everyone's intro was spot on, for this new initiative, the Re:VISION Live...
詳しいことは概要欄やホロアースの公式ホームページをご確認ください！
For details, please check the description box or the official Holoearth website!
はい！ということでね、今日はでもみんながね、アバターで参加してるし…
Yes! So today, since everyone is participating as avatars...
いろんな角度からのこの振り付け、確認してほしいなと思います！
We hope you'll check out the choreography from various angles!
ねねの服着てる人はいると信じてるからな、みんな！
I believe there are people wearing Nene's outfit, okay, everyone!
いる！いるから！もっとよく映してー！
There are! They're here! Show it off more!
いいよいいよー！
Looking good, looking good~!
あ、いいよ！こっちが写真撮るんだね！
Oh, nice! So we're taking photos over here!
みんなとやれること何かない？おまる。
Is there something we can do together with everyone, Omaru?
え、何かなー？
Eh, like what?
よし、あれやろう、あれ！えーと、走りましょう、皆さん！
Alright, let's do that thing! Um, let's run, everyone!
おっ、走るか！
Oh, let's run!
走るよ！ここから！
We're going to run! Starting from here!
ポルカが先頭で、ぐるーっと走ってみよう！
With Polka leading the way, let's run all the way around!
オッケー！じゃあみんな集合！
Okay! Everyone assemble, assemble!
みんなついてきてねー！
Everyone, follow us~!
じゃあ、せーので行くか！せーの！
Alright, shall we go on "ready, set"? Ready, set!
うわーー！
Whoa~~~!
先生！速いヤツがいます！
Teacher! Someone's running super fast!
あれ！？
Huh!?
はい！はい！はい！早くしてください！
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up please!
ちょっと！ついてこれないよ！
Hey! They can't keep up with you!
本気奴がいます！
Someone's going full tryhard mode!
本気のヤツが！
Someone's seriously sprinting!
速いよー！半周遅れです、こっち！
So fast~! We're half a lap behind over here!
半周遅れ！
Half a lap behind!
出遅れてる？逆に。
Did we fall behind? Or the opposite?
ゴール！お疲れ様ー！
Goal! Great job, everyone~!
みんなと走れて楽しーい！
Running with everyone was so much fun~!
一緒に走れること、なかなか無いからねー。
It's not often we get to run together like this.
ちなみにですね、本番の曲の最中ですが…
By the way, during the actual songs...
周りの人がね、ジャンプすると見えやすいように配慮してください！
Please be mindful so that people around you can see easily when jumping!
ピピッ！
Pipip!
前寄りの人に配慮して！
Be considerate of the people in front of you!
配慮して！
Be considerate!
はい！盛り上がってるところ申し訳ないんですが…
Alright! We hate to interrupt while everyone's having so much fun, but...
ここで、悲しいお知らせがあります…
We have a sad announcement to make here...
えー！？何々ー！？
Eh~!? What is it~!?
ということで皆さん、すみません。
So, everyone, we're sorry.
YouTubeとホロアースのエントランスにあるフォーカルスクエアでの無料配信はここまでとなっております。
The free broadcast on YouTube and at Focal Square in the Holoearth entrance ends here.
すみません
Excuse me.
引き続き ホロハース...最後ではライブが配信されますので
The concert will continue to be streamed until the end in Holoearth,
YouTubeで見ている方は 動画の概要欄をチェックしてください
so if you're watching on YouTube, please check the description box!
はい！
Got it!
で チケット持っている方で まだこっちに来てない フォーカルスクエアのみんなは よかったらこっちに来てください
And for those with tickets who are still in Focal Square, please head on over here!
来てください
Come on over!
じゃあ というわけで...
So, with that being said...
YouTubeのみんな バイバーイ！
Everyone on YouTube, bye-bye!
爽やかだな
That was so crisp.
というわけで 次からはソロ曲ですが
Moving on, next up are the solo songs!
まずは 誰からかな？
First up, who's going to perform first?
誰かな 誰かな 誰かな 誰かな...
Who could it be? Who could it be?
ねねちゃん！
Nene-chan!
それでは よろしく！
All right, take it away!
みんな どんどん盛り上がって行くぞ！
Everyone, let's keep this energy going!
イエーイ！
Yeah!